khantv.com 2012-01-13

# Live Cricket - Watch Cricket Streaming, Watch Live Cricket | Free

KhanTV Privacy Policy 

At KhanTV, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our web site, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. 

KhanTV, which operates the Internet sites located at KhanTV.com, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our sites. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. Personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites. In those instances when we do collect personally identifiable information, the following policies apply: 

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Notice**  
KhanTV will notify you when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you and how we intend to use it. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with information you requested, in connection with entry forms, or in connection with community postings such as chat and bulletin boards. Sometimes KhanTV engages in activities with business partners and sponsors with whom personal information is jointly collected or shared. We will try to make it clear at the time of collection who is asking for and/or sharing your information. In situations where your information will be shared, it is recommended that you also review the privacy policy of our business partner or sponsor. 

**Use and Security**  
Personally identifiable information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Such other uses may include sending you information or materials we think you will find interesting, or sharing the information with KhanTV's Media's advertisers and reputable business partners. However, at the time of collection, you will have the option of instructing us not to send you additional information or share your personal information with third parties. KhanTV is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of our business partners. 

KhanTV may use reputable third parties to manage activities available on our sites including, but not limited to statistical analysis, or chats. These parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. Similarly, we may contract with third parties to handle the fulfillment of subscriptions or requests for information you submit to our sites, such as sending you a newsletter. In most instances, KhanTV instructs these third parties to use personally identifiable information only for the specific purpose for which it is collected, and not to sell, market or transfer such information to other entities. If KhanTV obtains personal information that has been collected from you by a third party, including our business partners, this Privacy Policy nonetheless governs KhanTV's use of that information. 

Please remember that any information posted on bulletin boards and/or communicated in chat areas becomes public information. You should use caution when sharing information as any of it can be collected and used by people you may not know. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to divulge any personal information. While KhanTV strives to protect and respect your privacy, we can not guarantee the security of any information you disclose in a chat room or bulletin board and you do so at your own risk. 

KhanTV may use personally identifiable information in aggregate form to make our sites better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by KhanTV or provided to others, in aggregate, for marketing, advertising or research purposes. 

If at any time after submitting your personal information to our sites you would no longer like to receive information from us, please let us know by using the "Contact Us" link on our main page. 

Personal information may be disclosed in special situations where KhanTV has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with KhanTV's rights, property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, KhanTV may reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

KhanTV maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our sites, and periodically reviews and updates its security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Although KhanTV strives to protect your personal information, we can not ensure or warranty the security of any information you may transmit to us. This is done so at your own risk. Once we do receive your transmission, however, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value you privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPRA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, KhanTV makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
KhanTV does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Google and the DoubleClick DART Cookie  
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on KhanTV.com.   
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.   
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners may include Google Adsense, Adbrite, .. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on KhanTV. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

KhanTV has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. KhanTV's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Links to Third Party and Co-Branded Sites**  
KhanTV has established many links directly to sites operated by third parties. These sites are not operated or maintained by KhanTV. These sites may collect personal information from you. You should check the applicable privacy policy's of the third party site's in case you enter these sites. All links to external sites (not KhanTV's) are opened in a new window! 

KhanTV chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, KhanTV is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by KhanTV of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you enter a third party site by such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. 

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our  Terms of use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

**Still have questions?**  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to Send Us E-mail to admin@khantv.com   
KhanTV.Com
